Hey, where are you going?
Before you leave, I have a question.
How much money are you leaving on the table by not having a conversation with your clients regarding planning for long-term care?
Unfortunately, there are only one of two things that happen as we get older.
We either die, or our body and brain starts to fail us, and we find ourselves looking to others to help with our everyday activities
of daily living such as bathing, dressing, feeding, toileting, transferring, and maintaining our continence.
Take a look at the quick calculations on the screen below.
You decide how many new clients or policies you can sell in a year, and the commission revenue numbers take care of themselves.
We have a motto: if you don't ask, you don't get.
So why not ask your clients if they've considered the emotional, physical, and financial consequences of not planning for long-term care?
If you don't, your competition just might.
We hope to see you return to try out this long-term care asset utilization modeling tool.
Thanks for visiting.